export const quiz = {
  topic: 'Javascript',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 4,
  perQuestionScore: 5,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'When does the Oktoberfest start in Germany?',
      choices: ['October', 'November', 'January', 'September'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'September',
    },
    {
      question: "What's Apfelschorle?",
      choices: ['Apple juice with soda', 'Grape juice', 'Orange juice with ice', 'Mixed fruit juice with soda'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Apple juice with soda',
    },
    {
      question: 'What are "french fries" called in Germany?',
      choices: ['Fritzies', 'Fritzen', 'Fritten', 'Fritters'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Fritten',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which treaty established the legal basis for Lutheranism in Germany?',
      choices: ['Treaties of Holland', 'Edict of Milan', 'Peace of Westphalia', 'Peace of Augsburg'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Peace of Augsburg',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who declared that the great issues of the day would be decided by “blood and iron” and later was the founder and first chancellor of the German Empire?',
      choices: ['Frederick I', 'Adolf Hitler', 'Otto von Bismarck', 'William I'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Otto von Bismarck',
    },
    {
      question: 'What city was the favourite residence of Charlemagne and later the principal coronation site of medieval German kings?',
      choices: ['Aachen', 'Berlin', 'Vienna', 'Cologne'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Aachen',
    },
    {
      question: 'What was the only major encounter between German and British fleets in World War I?',
      choices: ['Second battle of Somme', 'Battle of Jutland', 'Battle of Britain', 'Berlin blockade'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Battle of Jutland',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who helped create the Gestapo, the police force of the German Third Reich?',
      choices: ['Erwin Rommel', 'Gustav Stresemann', 'Hermann Göring', 'Adolf Hitler'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Hermann Göring',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of these are famous German dishes?',
      choices: ['Brot & Brötchen', 'Käsespätzle', 'Schnitzel', 'All of the above'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'All of the above',
    },
    {
      question: 'Sauerbraten is usually served with which of the following as accompaniment?',
      choices: ['Potato pancakes', 'Carrot slices', 'Minced cucumber', 'Mashed eggplant'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Potato pancakes',
    },
  ],
}